Register of the Ferdinand I, Czar of Bulgaria Papers, 1846-1956
Hoover Institution Archives
- CHRONOLOGICAL FILE, 1846-1956
  - 1914
    - World War I - German campaigns (Folder 13)
    - Miscellenous (Folder 14)
  - 1915
    - Correspondence
      - General (Folder 15)
      - Bainbridge, Oliver (Folder 16)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Athens (Folder 17)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Belgrade (Folder 18)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Berlin (Folder 19)
      - Bulgarian Legation in London and The Hague (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Petrograd (Folder 2)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Vienna (Folder 3-4)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Washington, D.C. (Folder 5)
      - Bulgarian military attaches abroad (Folder 6-7)
      - Congratulatory telegrams (Folder 8)
      - Glavnokomanduiushch na Deistvuiushchata Armiia (Folder 9)
      - Hochenlohe-Langenburg, Ernst (Folder 10)
      - Incoming (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
      - Karavelova, E. (Folder 3)
      - Kobachev, General (Folder 4)
      - Kosev, Paro (Folder 5)
      - O'Mahony, Pierce (Folder 6)
    - Ganchev, Colonel, reports (Folder 7-9)
    - Ganchev, Colonel, reports (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Maps (Folder 2)
    - Reports
      - General (Folder 3-4)
      - Military (Folder 5)
    - Savvov, General, report (Folder 6)
    - Voennata Akademia (Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 8)
  - 1916
    - Bulgaria
      - Miliary affairs (Folder 9)
      - Military war bulletins (Folder 10)
      - Military war bulletin (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
      - Politics and government (Folder 3)
      - Railroads (Folder 4)
    - Clippings and press summaries (Folder 5-9)
    - Correspondence
      - General (Box 56, Folder 1-3)
      - Boiadzhiev, General (Folder 4)
      - Bulgarian Consulate General in Budapest (Folder 5-6)
      - Bulgarian Consulate General in Smyrna (Folder 7)
      - Bulgarian Consulate General in Solun (Folder 8)
      - Bulgarian diplomatic outposts in various countries (Folder 9)
      - Bulgarian Legation at The Hague (Folder 10)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Athens (Folder 11)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Berlin (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Berne (Folder 2)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Bucharest (Folder 3)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Constantinople (Folder 4-5)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Paris (Folder 6)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Stockholm (Folder 7)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Vienna (Folder 8-9)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Vienna (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Washington, D.C. (Folder 4)
      - Bulgarian military attaches abroad (Folder 5)
      - Diplomatic (Folder 6)
      - Glavnokomanduiushchi na Deistvuiushchata Armiia (Folder 7)
      - Glavnokomanduiushchi na Deistvuiushchata Armiia (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Incoming (Folder 2-6)
      - Incoming (Box 60, Folder 1-7)
      - Incoming (Box 61, Folder 1-4)
      - Mefodii, Mitropolit (Folder 5)
      - Ministr na Finansite (Folder 6)
      - Ministr Predsedatel' (Folder 7-8)
      - Murany, Graf von (Folder 9)
      - Sapunarov, Colonel (Folder 10)
      - Telegrams
        - Cabinet Chief (Box 62, Folder 1)
        - Coded (Folder 2)
        - Foreign heads of state (Folder 3)
      - War Ministry (Folder 4)
      - Wilhelm, Kaiser (Folder 5)
    - Ganchev, Colonel, reports (Folder 6-9)
    - Muhlens, Professor, reports (in German) (Folder 19)
    - Russia, conditions and events, including assassination of Rasputin, reports (in German) (Folder 20)
    - Speeches, typewritten (in German) (Folder 12)
    - Stanchov, Colonel, reports (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - World War I, reports (in German) and maps (Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 3-7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 1-3)
  - 1917
    - Clippings (Folder 4)
    - Correspondence
      - General (Folder 5-7)
      - General (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
      - Bulgarian Consulate General in Budapest (Folder 3)
      - Bulgarian Consulate General in Hamburg (Folder 4)
      - Bulgarian Legation at The Hague (Folder 5)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Berlin (Folder 6)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Berne (Folder 7)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Constantinople (Folder 8)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Stockholm (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Vienna (Folder 3-6)
      - Bulgarian military attaches (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Foreign heads of state (Folder 2)
      - Incoming (Folder 3-4)
      - Predsedatel' na Ministerskiia Svet (Folder 5)
      - Shchab na Deistvuiushchata Armiia (Folder 6)
      - Tantilov, Colonel (Folder 7)
      - Tantilov, Colonel (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Telegrams (Folder 2)
    - Ganchev, Colonel, reports (Folder 3-4)
    - Stanchev, Colonel, reports (Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 69, Folder 1-3)
  - 1918
    - Bulgaria
      - Churches (Folder 4)
      - Foreign policy (Folder 5)
      - Foreign relations
        - Germany (Folder 6)
        - Turkey (Folder 7)
        - United States of America (Folder 8)
      - Military affairs (Folder 9)
      - Military affairs (Box 70, Folder 1-2)
      - Military bulletins (Folder 3)
    - Clippings and press summaries (Folder 4-5)
    - Correspondence
      - General (Folder 6)
      - Bulgarian Consulate General in Budapest (Folder 7)
      - Bulgarian Consulate in Smyrna (Folder 8)
      - Bulgarian Legation at The Hague (Folder 9)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Berne (Folder 10)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Kiev (Folder 11)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Moscow (Folder 12)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Stockholm (Folder 13)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Tsarigrad (Box 71, Folder 1-3)
      - Bulgarian Legation in Vienna (Folder 4-6)
      - Bulgarian Military Attache in Berne (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Chaprashikov, S. (Folder 2)
      - Ganchev, Colonel (Folder 3)
      - Gruev, Secretary (Folder 4)
      - Incoming (Folder 5-8)
      - Incoming (Box 73, Folder 1-6)
      - Incoming (Box 74, Folder 1-5)
      - Kaiserlich Deutscher Militar-Bevollmachtichter (Folder 6)
      - Karl, Kaiser und Konig (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Outgoing (Folder 2)
      - Predsedatel' na Ministerskiia Svet (Folder 3)
      - Tantilov, Colonel (Folder 4)
    - Decrees and orders (Folder 5)
    - Ganchev, Colonel, reports (in Bulgarian) (Folder 6)
    - Musalla mountains (Folder 7)
    - World War I, reports (in German) (Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 1-2)
  - 1919, general (Folder 3-4)
  - 1920, general (Folder 5)
  - 1921, general (Folder 6)
  - 1922, general (Folder 7)
  - 1923, general (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - 1924, general (Folder 2)
  - 1925, general (Folder 3)
  - 1926, general (Folder 4)
  - 1927, general (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - 1928, general (Folder 2-3)
  - 1928-29, telegrams (Folder 4)
  - 1929, general (Folder 5)
  - 1929, general (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - 1929-1930, telegrams (Folder 2)
  - 1930, general (Folder 3-4)
  - 1930-31, telegrams (Folder 5-6)
  - 1931, general (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
  - 1932
    - General (Folder 3-5)
    - General (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Telegrams (Folder 2)
  - 1932-34, telegrams (Folder 3)
  - 1933
    - General (Folder 4-5)
    - General (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Telegrams (Folder 2)
  - 1933-35, telegrams (Folder 3)
  - 1934
    - General (Folder 4-5)
    - General (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Telegrams (Folder 2-3)
  - 1934-35, telegrams (Folder 4)
  - 1935
    - General (Folder 5-6)
    - Telegrams (Box 84, Folder 1-2)
  - 1936, general (Folder 3-6)
  - 1936, general (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - 1936-38, telegrams (Folder 2)
  - 1937
    - General (Folder 3-4)
    - Telegrams (Folder 5)
  - 1938, general (Folder 6)
  - 1938, general (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - 1939, general (Folder 2-3)
  - 1940, general (Folder 4-5)
  - 1941, general (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - 1942, general (Folder 2-3)
  - 1943, general (Folder 4-5)
  - 1944, general (Folder 6)
  - 1945, general (Folder 7)
  - 1946, general (Folder 8)
  - 1946, general (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
  - 1947, general (Folder 3)
  - 1948, general (Folder 4-6)
  - 1956, general (Folder 7)